<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>C++ |</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/tags/c++/</link><atom:link href="https://lilab-bcb.github.io/tags/c++/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>C++</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/media/logo.svg</url><title>C++</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/tags/c++/</link></image><item><title>PROBer</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/prober/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/prober/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;PROBer is the first unified probabilistic framework for the analysis of a diverse set of sequencing-based ‘toeprinting’ assays. These assays are used to probe RNA secondary structure (DMS/SHAPE-Seq), detect epitranscriptomic mark (Pseudo-Seq), or identify RNA-protein interaction (iCLIP/eCLIP), which are important to understanding post-transcriptional gene regulation from all aspects.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>DETONATE</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/detonate/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/detonate/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;DETONATE (DE novo TranscriptOme rNa-seq Assembly with or without the Truth Evaluation) is a de novo transcriptome assembly evaluation package, which contains two components, RSEM-EVAL and REF-EVAL. Bo developed the RSEM-EVAL component.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>CSEM</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/csem/</link><pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/csem/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;CSEM (ChIP-Seq multi-read allocation using Expectation-Maximization) is one of the first ChIP-Seq multi-mapping read allocators, which allows multi-reads to be utilized by peak callers.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>RSEM</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/rsem/</link><pubDate>Mon, 15 Feb 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/rsem/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;RSEM (RNA-Seq by Expectation-Maximization) is a widely-used RNA-Seq transcript quantification tool. RSEM papers are cited over 5,300 times. It was served in nationwide consortium projects such as ENCODE (The Encyclopedia of DNA Elements) and TCGA (The Cancer Genome Altas). It is also recommended by HCA (Human Cell Atlas) for analyzing plate-based SMART-Seq2 single-cell RNA-Seq data.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>