<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Python |</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/tags/python/</link><atom:link href="https://lilab-bcb.github.io/tags/python/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Python</description><generator>Hugo Blox Builder (https://hugoblox.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/media/logo.svg</url><title>Python</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/tags/python/</link></image><item><title>Pegasus</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/pegasus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/pegasus/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Pegasus is a tool for analyzing transcriptomes of millions of single cells. It is a command line tool, a python package and a base for Cloud-based analysis workflows.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Harmony-Pytorch</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/harmony-pytorch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/harmony-pytorch/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Harmony-PyTorch is an efficient PyTorch implementation of Harmony algorithm, used for data integration and batch correction.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It has been adopted by
(a GPU-accelerated single-cell analysis python package designed specific for NVIDIA devices; part of
) for its implementation on Harmony batch correction method. See
.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Cirrocumulus</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/cirrocumulus/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/cirrocumulus/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Cirrocumulus is an interactive visualization tool for large-scale single-cell genomics data, with the following features:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Visualize datasets in h5ad, 10x h5, Xenium, loom, Seurat, TileDB, or zarr formats&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;View MERFISH or other spatial transcriptomics data overlaid on an image&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Easily deploy on a laptop, on-premise server, cloud VM, or Google App Engine&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share the current visualization state in a URL&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Share datasets securely with collaborators&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Create dotplots, heatmaps, and violin plots to explore relationships between categorical variables and expression&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generate composition plots to inspect cluster makeup&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore complete differential expression results generated by Scanpy or Pegasus/Cumulus&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Interactively create and share “AND” or “OR” filters&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Collaboratively annotate cell types in real time, optionally using a controlled vocabulary (example ontology)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Quickly load multiple features from predefined lists (see example)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Explore multiple features and embeddings simultaneously&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Fast interactive exploration of 2 and 3-d embeddings of millions of cells, including zoom, pan, rotate (3-d), and lasso tools&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Save publication quality images&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Highly customizable - for example, set the color map, point size, or whether to use fog for 3-d embeddings to fade distant points&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;</description></item><item><title>NMF-Torch</title><link>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/nmf-torch/</link><pubDate>Tue, 30 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://lilab-bcb.github.io/software/nmf-torch/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;NMF-Torch is a PyTorch implementation on Non-negative Matrix Factorization. It provides both batch and online modes for updating the matrices during computation, and aims for high efficiency.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>